Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 7 Locals, 2.
  - Local 714
    - Local 714 Outgoing Correspondence, August 30, 1944-January 15, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 49)
      - Manner to UE Regarding Finances, 4.
      - Roy Seville Letter Regarding Supplies, August 4, 1950; 5.
      - Seville to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, February 1, 1951; 6.
      - Seville to Emspak Regarding Election, January 15, 1952; 7.
      - John Steele to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 26, 1945; 8.
      - Alfred Zuber to Emspak Regarding Strike, September 1945; 9.
      - Zuber Letter Regarding Finances, August 30, 1944; 10.
      - Zuber Letter Regarding Contract, July 8, 1946; 11.
    - Local 714 Organization, December 14, 1943-January 13, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Haug, December 14, 1943; 1.
      - Haug to Emspak, December 14, 1943; 2.
      - Haug to Emspak, December 17, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Haug, December 22, 1943; 4.
      - Haug to Emspak, December 29, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Haug, January 7, 1944; 6.
      - Haug to Emspak, January 7, 1944; 7.
      - Emspak to Victor Decavitch, January 12, 1944; 8.
      - Emspak to Haug, January 13, 1944; 9-10.
    - Local 714 Per Capita Withholdings, September 1-8, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Julius Emspak to Victor Decavitch with August 30, 1944, Alfred Zuber Letter, September 1, 1944; 1.
      - Decavitch to Emspak, September 8, 1944; 2.
    - Local 714 Bluffton Triplett Electric, August 6, 1936-March 3, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Local 714 Strike, September 17-November 4, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - J.E. Carroll to Philip Murray, September 17, 1946; 1.
      - Allan Haywood to Albert Fitzgerald, September 19, 1946; 2.
      - Haywood to Carroll, September 19, 1946; 3.
      - Victor Decavitch to Julius Emspak, October 2, 1946; 4.
      - Herbert Hirshberg to James Matles, November 4, 1946; 5.
    - Local 714 Strike Correspondence, February 22, 1972-June 18, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Local 714 Bluffton Triplette Electric, March 15, 1937-July 29, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Local 714 Sandusky Correspondence, October 2, 1956-May 19, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Local 714 Sandusky G & C Foundry Correspondence and Receipts, July 31, 1992-December 2, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Local 714 Correspondence, October 11, 1945-November 20, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - J.K. Smith to Julius Emspak Regarding Strike, October 11, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Herbert Hirshberg Regarding Per Capita, August 8, 1950; 2.
      - Emspak to Hirshberg Regarding Finances, February 6, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to Hirshberg Regarding Finances and Officers, January 22, 1952; 4.
      - Hirshberg to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 25, 1952; 5.
      - Bert Washington to Emspak, November 20, 1952; 6.
  - Local 715
    - Local 715 Officers Lists, December 30, 1941-January 29, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Local 715 Constitution, December 29, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Local 715 Incoming Correspondence, September 30, 1941-January 5, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Bill Cahn to Vernon Law Regarding Publications, April 11, 1949; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to David Turner Regarding Supplies, September 30, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to George Bender Regarding Officers List, January 5, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to Bender Regarding Bonding, January 15, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Bender Regarding Local Organization, January 30, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Bender Regarding Supplies, February 26, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to Bender Regarding Telegram, May 1, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Bender Regarding Finances, October 19, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to H. Ersman Regarding Supplies, May 6, 1943; 9.
      - Emspak to Howard Mooney Regarding Bonding, August 11, 1943; 10.
      - Emspak to Ersman Regarding Finances, November 11, 1943; 11.
      - Emspak to Mooney Regarding Letter, March 9, 1944; 12.
      - Emspak to John Janowitz Regarding Fees, February 16, 1945; 13.
      - Emspak to Lucille Kapunscinski Regarding Benefits, August 26, 1946; 14.
      - Emspak to Guy Troyan Regarding Supplies, April 4, 1947; 15.
      - Emspak to John Jerse Regarding Finances, August 3, 1950; 16.
      - James Matles to Donald Turner Regarding Contracts, October 23, 1941; 17.
      - Clifford McAvoy to William Randall Regarding Finances, June 25, 1946; 18.
      - Don Pinkston to Charles Ermer Regarding Publications, November 27, 1945; 19.
      - David Rosston to Local 715 Regarding Bonding, May 14, 1943; 20.
    - Local 715 Outgoing Correspondence, October 21, 1941-July 31, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - George Bender to Julius Emspak Regarding Bonding, January 13, 1942; 1.
      - Bender to Emspak Regarding Membership List, January 26, 1942; 2.
      - Bender to Emspak Regarding Bonding, February 23, 1942; 3.
      - Bender to Emspak Regarding Price Control, April 26, 1942; 4.
      - Charles Eimer to UE Regarding Publications, 5.
      - Harry Eisman to Emspak Regarding Dues, November 9, 1943; 6.
      - John Janowitz to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 31, 1950; 7.
      - John Jerse to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 31, 1950; 8.
      - Lucille Kapuscinski to Janet Barish Regarding Benefits, August 7, 1946; 9.
      - Howard Mooney to Emspak Regarding Contract, February 29, 1944; 10.
      - John Phillips to Emspak Regarding Staff Assignment, May 28, 1943; 11.
      - William Randall to C. McAvoy Regarding Finances, May 25, 1946; 12.
      - Guy Troyan to Emspak Regarding Resolution, February 28, 1947; 13.
      - Troyan to Phillip Murray Regarding Resolution, February 28, 1947; 14.
      - Troyan to Emspak Regarding Board Decision, March 19, 1947; 15.
      - Troyan to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 19, 1947; 16.
      - Troyan to John Burns Regarding Union Condemnation, April 22, 1947; 17.
      - Troyan to Local 813 Regarding Union Support, September 27, 1948; 18.
      - Troyan to Charles Kersten Regarding Protest, September 27, 1948; 19.
      - Troyan to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding News in Issues, October 12, 1949; 20.
      - Troyan to Murray Regarding Strike Support, October 12, 1949; 21.
      - David Turner to Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 21, 1941; 22.
      - Turner to Emspak Regarding Requested Organizers, September 27, 1942; 23.
    - Local 715 Financial Bonding, February 26, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Local 715 Financial Report, March 1944 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Local 715 Per Capita, November 9-12, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Haug, November 9, 1943; 1.
      - Haug to Emspak, November 12, 1943; 2.
    - Local 715 Mailing List, October 3-8, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Herbert Hirshberg to Julius Emspak, October 3, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Hirshberg, October 8, 1951; 2.
    - Local 715 Cleveland Reliance Electric, April 6, 1937-January 31, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Local 715 Cleveland Reliance Electric, March 11, 1937-August 23, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Local 715 Correspondence, Fred Keller Memo to James Matles Regarding Strike, February 1950 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Local 716
    - Local 716 Officers Lists, December 22-April 16, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Local 716 Constitution, January 9, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Local 716 Incoming Correspondence, September 30, 1943-December 3, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Julius Emspak to Ms Clayton Regarding Bonding, September 30, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Joseph Hicks Regarding Bonding, April 28, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Lilliam Wade Regarding Bonding, February 7, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Wade Regarding Bonding, December 11, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Wade Regarding Forwarded Information, February 25, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Wade Regarding Finances, March 1, 1946; 6.
      - Emspak to Sara White Regarding Finances, November 17, 1948; 7.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Wade Regarding Consititution, September 11, 1944; 8.
      - Fitzgerald to C. Saller Regarding Letter, January 7, 1947; 9.
      - Herbert Hirshberg to Louise Brogle Regarding Officer Secession, December 3, 1949; 10.
      - Hirshberg to Local 716 Officers Regarding Revoked Membership, December 3, 1949; 11.
    - Local 716 Outgoing Correspondence, November 21, 1943-July 21, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Donald Duston to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 22, 1946; 1.
      - Maggie Grant to UE Regarding Supplies, July 21, 1949; 2.
      - Grant to UE Regarding Officers, August 10, 1949; 3.
      - Joseph Hacks to UE Regarding Bonding, April 25, 1944; 4.
      - Thelma James to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 21, 1943; 5.
      - Lonia Mae Rico to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 7, 1948; 6.
      - Rico Letter Regarding Bonding, June 24, 1948; 7.
      - Eleanor Rodgers to Louise Brogle Regarding Lay-offs, July 21, 1949; 8.
      - Rodgers to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations, 9.
      - N. Sallie to Fitzgerald Regarding Termination, December 30, 1949; 10.
      - Lillian Wade Letter Regarding Constitution, September 8, 1944; 11.
      - Wade to Emspak Regarding Bonding, January 28, 1945; 12.
      - Wade Letter Regarding Finances, February 20, 1945; 13.
      - Wade Letter Regarding Finances, 14.
    - Local 716 Cleveland Grahling Electric, April 8, 1937-January 26, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Local 716 Cleveland Grahling Electric Finances, April 1, 1937-June 14, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Local 716 Organization, September 20-October 13, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - Julius Emspak to Leo Turner, September 20, 1943; 1.
      - Turner to Emspak, October 2, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Turner, October 3, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Turner, October 13, 1943; 4.
    - Local 716 Correspondence, April 5, 1944-November 19, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Haug Regarding Per Capita, April 5, 1944; 1.
      - Joseph Vejlupek to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 6, 1946; 2.
      - Richard Niebur to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, June 16, 1947; 3.
      - Joseph Persily to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, November 19, 1949; 4.
  - Local 717
    - Local 717 Officers Lists, November 12, 1943-January 20, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Local 717 Executive Board Minutes, March 4, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Local 717 Constitution, August 8, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Local 717 Warren Sunlight Electric, April 10-December 30, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Local 717 Membership Minutes, November 1, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Local 717 Resolutions, July 25, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Local 717 Incoming Correspondence, July 17, 1941-October 13, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Julius Emspak Letter Regarding Bonding, July 17, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Roy Stein Regarding Constitution, October 27, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Edward Luscombe Regarding Audit, September 21, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Charles Parker Regarding Bonding, March 30, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Ella Mae Garner Regarding Staff Assignment, December 29, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Parker Regarding Staff Assignments, December 29, 1943; 6.
      - Emspak to Garner Regarding Letter, January 3, 1944; 7.
      - Emspak to Parker Regarding Finances, March 13, 1944; 8.
      - Emspak to Parker Regarding Questionnaire, April 8, 1944; 9.
      - Emspak to Parker Regarding Fees, February 16, 1945; 10.
      - Emspak to John McFall Regarding Check, October 26, 1945; 11.
      - Emspak to Sid Sayers Regarding Dues, January 8, 1945; 12.
      - Emspak to Local 717 Regarding Supplies, October 22, 1947; 13.
      - Emspak to James Sayers Regarding Resolution, November 10, 1947; 14.
      - Emspak to Homer Pierce Regarding Finances, July 30, 1948; 15.
      - Emspak to J. Sayers Regarding Fees, September 12, 1949; 16.
      - Emspak to J. Sayers Regarding Strike, October 13, 1949; 17.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to John Beskid Regarding Staff Assignments, November 8, 1942; 18.
      - Fitzgerald to Luscombe Regarding Meeting Procedures, November 18, 1942; 19.
      - Fitzgerald to Luscombe Regarding Letter, February 8, 1943; 20.
      - Fitzgerald to Luscombe Regarding Amalgamation, December 3, 1943; 21.
      - Fitzgerald to Parker Regarding Resolution, August 23, 1946; 22.
      - Norma Gould to Parker Regarding Letter, February 11, 1943; 23.
    - Local 717 Incoming Correspondence, March 5, 1941-July 13, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - James Matles to Victor Decavitch Regarding Contract, March 5, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Decavitch Regarding Meeting, March 18, 1941; 2.
      - Matles to Decavitch Regarding Meeting, March 24, 1941; 3.
      - Matles to Decavitch Regarding Finances, March 26, 1942; 4.
      - Matles to Arthur Garfield Regarding Stoppage, April 5, 1941; 5.
      - Matles to Decavitch Regarding Finances, April 18, 1941; 6.
      - Matles to Decavitch Regarding Finances, May 15, 1941; 7.
      - Matles to Decavitch Regarding Finances, June 25, 1941; 8.
      - Matles to Decavitch Regarding Conference, July 23, 1941; 9.
      - Matles to M. Burkhart Regarding Apprenticeship, August 12, 1941; 10.
      - Matles to Burkhart Regarding Contract, August 14, 1941; 11.
      - Matles to Burkhart Regarding Apprenticeship, August 25, 1941; 12.
      - Matles to Burkhart Regarding Grievances, September 17, 1941; 13.
      - Matles to Roy Stein Regarding Constitution, September 22, 1941; 14.
      - Matles to John Beskid Regarding Negotiations, October 2, 1941; 15.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Conference, October 3, 1941; 16.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Grievances, October 13, 1941; 17.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Wage Rate, October 17, 1941; 18.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Grievances, November 10, 1941; 19.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Materials, December 3, 1942; 20.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Work Divisions, January 14, 1942; 21.
      - Matles to Charles Parker Regarding Letter, February 19, 1943; 22.
      - Matles to Edward Luscombe Regarding Company Actions, April 20, 1943; 23.
      - Matles to Luscombe Regarding Letter, June 25, 1943; 24.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Letter, December 13, 1945; 25.
      - Matles to Parker Regarding Briefs, December 13, 1945; 26.
      - Matles to Parker Regarding Wages, February 14, 1946; 27.
      - Matles to Homer Pierce Regarding Forwarded Information, November 8, 1948; 28.
      - Matles to Pierce Regarding Forwarded Information, December 15, 1948; 29.
      - Matles to James Sayers Regarding Letter, April 5, 1949; 30.
      - Matles to Sayers Regarding Finances, April 28, 1949; 31.
      - Matles to Edward Wedman Regarding Forwarded Information, July 13, 1949; 32.
      - Matles to Beskid Regarding Forwarded Information, 33.
    - Local 717 Incoming Correspondence, July 16, 1941-November 12, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 86)
      - Thomas Neil to Angeo DeJacimo Regarding Finances, January 31, 1946; 1.
      - Albert Olson to Roy Stein Regarding Finances, July 16, 1941; 2.
      - David Ratner to Charles Parker Regarding Finances, March 12, 1946; 3.
      - David Scribner to Edward Luscombe Regarding Letter, December 4, 1943; 4.
      - Scribner to James Ayres Regarding Election, November 12, 1947; 5.
      - L. Uhlir to John Beskid Regarding Grievances, August 5, 1941; 6.
      - Uhlir to Maurice Burchart Regarding Meeting, August 7, 1941; 7.
      - Uhlir to Burchart Regarding Rates, October 9, 1941; 8.
    - Local 717 Outgoing Correspondence, April 12, 1941-February 20, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - John Beskid to James Matles Regarding Conferences, July 22, 1941; 1.
      - Beskid to Matles Regarding Rates, September 10, 1941; 2.
      - Beskid to Matles Regarding Meeting, October 3, 1941; 3.
      - Beskid to Matles Regarding Grievances, October 10, 1941; 4.
      - Beskid to Matles Regarding Strike, November 13, 1941; 5.
      - Beskid to Matles Regarding Proposals, December 19, 1941; 6.
      - Beskid to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Request, November 18, 1942; 7.
      - Beskid to Matles Regarding Forwarded Information, December 3, 1942; 8.
      - Beskid to David Scribner Regarding Veterans, November 20, 1945; 9.
      - Beskid to Matles Regarding Elections, December 4, 1945; 10.
      - M. Burchart to Matles Regarding Apprenticeship, August 7, 1941; 11.
      - Burchart to Matles Regarding Contract, August 13, 1941; 12.
      - Burchart to Matles Regarding Apprenticeship, August 21, 1941; 13.
      - Burchart to Matles Regarding Letter, August 21, 1941; 14.
      - Burchart to Matles Regarding Requested Information, August 21, 1941; 15.
      - Burchart to J. Estabrock Regarding Meeting, August 21, 1941; 16.
      - Victor Decavitch to Matles Regarding Contract, April 12, 1941; 17.
      - Decavitch to Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 2, 1941; 18.
      - Decavitch to Matles Regarding Staff Assignments, June 22, 1941; 19.
      - Decavitch to Matles Regarding Ratified Agreement, 20.
      - Ella Garner to Julius Emspak Regarding Amalgamation, December 31, 1943; 21.
      - Olga Kovach to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 20, 1945; 22.
      - Kovach to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 20, 1946; 23.
      - Edward Luscombe to Emspak Regarding Staff Assignments, August 3, 1942; 24.
      - Luscombe to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 4, 1942; 25.
      - Luscombe to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, November 5, 1942; 26.
    - Local 717 Outgoing Correspondence, January 4, 1943-December 3, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 88)
      - Edward Luscombe to Julius Emspak Regarding Officer List, January 4, 1943; 1.
      - Luscombe to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Finances, February 5, 1943; 2.
      - Luscombe to James Matles Regarding Grievances, April 15, 1943; 3.
      - Luscombe to Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 18, 1943; 4.
      - Luscombe to Hal Roach Regarding Meeting, September 9, 1943; 5.
      - Luscombe to Emspak Regarding Meeting, October 26, 1943; 6.
      - Luscombe to Emspak Regarding Bargaining, December 2, 1943; 7.
      - Luscombe to Matles Regarding Meeting Results, 8.
      - Charles Parker to Matles Regarding Letter, January 22, 1943; 9.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 25, 1943; 10.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Staff, December 13, 1943; 11.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 9, 1944; 12.
      - Parker to Neil Brant Regarding Resolution, May 12, 1944; 13.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Staff Change, June 7, 1944; 14.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Audit, July 13, 1944; 15.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Questionnaire, July 21, 1944; 16.
      - Parker to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Voting Procedures, August 19, 1944; 17.
      - Parker to B. MacGregor Regarding War Production, September 16, 1944; 18.
      - Parker to Victor Decavitch Regarding Leave of Absence, October 24, 1944; 19.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Fees, February 12, 1945; 20.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Motion, June 15, 1945; 21.
      - Parker to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 20, 1945; 22.
      - Parker to Matles Regarding Union Case, November 5, 945; 23.
      - Parker to Brant Regarding Meeting Results, November 20, 1945; 24.
      - Parker to Brant Regarding Negotiations, August 20, 1945; 25.
      - Parker to David Scribner Regarding Back Pay, March 7, 1946; 26.
      - Parker to Fitzgerald Regarding Resolutions, August 21, 1946; 27.
      - Parker to Matles Regarding Endorsed Conference Actions, December 3, 1946; 28.
    - Local 717 Outgoing Correspondence, August 15, 1941-October 7, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 89)
      - Homer Price to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 16, 1948; 1.
      - Price to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 30, 1948; 2.
      - Price to Arthur Garfield Regarding Publications, August 25, 1948; 3.
      - Price to James Matles Regarding Plant Organization, October 28, 1948; 4.
      - Sid Sayers to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 3, 1947; 5.
      - James Sayers to Neil Brant Regarding Ratified Agreement, April 17, 1947; 6.
      - J. Sayers to Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 2, 1947; 7.
      - J. Sayers to International Office Regarding Committee Members, June 27, 1947; 8.
      - J. Sayers to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 4, 1947; 9.
      - J. Sayers to Matles Regarding Briefs, March 31, 1949; 10.
      - J. Sayers to Emspak Regarding Fees, September 9, 1949; 11.
      - J. Sayers to Matles Regarding Condemned Staff Actions, 12.
      - J. Sayers to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, October 7, 1949; 13.
      - Roy Stein to Emspak Regarding Committee Appointment, August 15, 1941; 14.
      - Stein to Matles Regarding Staff Change, September 8, 1941; 15.
      - Stein to Matles Regarding Constitution, September 17, 1941; 16.
      - Stein to Emspak Regarding Staff Changes, July 8, 1942; 17.
      - Executive Board to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, November 18, 1942; 18.
    - Local 717 Warren Sunlight Electric, April 16, 1937-August 16, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Local 717 Newspaper, The Eye Opener, June 1949 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Local 717 Leaflets, January 26, 1941-June 1, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - "GM Meeting", January 26, 1941; 1.
      - "Wages Real Issue", June 1, 1949; 2.
      - "Petition", June 1949; 3.
      - "GM Workers", 4.
      - "Why Cry", 5.
      - "Speedup-Senority: The Real Issues", 6.
      - "Vote For.. .", 7.
    - Local 717 Grievances, January 7-August 29, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 93)
      - Grievance Form, January 7, 1941; 1.
      - Grievance Form, August 11, 1941; 2.
      - Grievance Statement with Time Cards, August 1941; 3.
      - H.W. Anderson to James Matles, August 29, 1941; 4.
    - Local 717 Amalgamation, June 22-December 4, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 94)
      - H.W. Anderson to James Matles, June 22, 1943; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Ella Mae Garner, October 28, 1943; 2.
      - Garner to Julius Emspak, November 1943; 3.
      - Emsak to Jean Blair, December 4, 1943; 4.
      - Agreement of Amalgamation, December 1943; 5.
      - Garner to Albert Fitzgerald, December 1943; 6.
    - Local 717 Staff Members, December 17-21, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 95)
      - Julius Emspak to Victor Decavitch, December 17, 1943; 1.
      - Decavitch to Emspak, December 21, 1943; 2.
    - Local 717 Political Action Committee, November 5-December 26, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 96)
      - Report on PAC Contributions, November 5, 1946; 1.
      - Returns of PAC Contributions, December 26, 1946; 2.
    - Local 717 Correspondence and Resolution Statement, October 9, 1942-November 8, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 97)
      - A.M. Cytle to the Men in the Armed Forces, October 9, 1942; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Victor Decavitch Regarding Factionalism, November 18, 1942; 2.
      - Fitzgerald to Decavitch, August 30, 1944; 3.
      - Paul Sheppard to Julius Emspak Regarding General Motors Contract, February 1946; 4.
      - Joint Wage Committee Resolution, April 15, 1947; 5.
      - James Matles to Robert Logsden Regarding Organization, November 8, 1948; 6.
    - Local 717 Grievances Regarding Job Classification, Wages and Productivity, January 25, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Local 718 (Springfield)
    - Local 718 (Springfield) Officers Lists, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Local 718 (Springfield) Constitution, October 4, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Local 718 (Springfield) Incoming Correspondence, April 23-July 11, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 101)
      - Julius Emspak to H. Dennison Regarding Officers List, April 23, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Everett Bateman Regarding Fees, May 27, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Bateman Regarding Supplies, July 11, 1947; 3.
    - Local 718 (Springfield) Outgoing Correspondence, July 10-September 12, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 102)
      - Everette Bateman to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 10, 1947; 1.
      - Henry Rodgers to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, August 20, 1947; 2.